It's hero time!
Ben 10: Race Against Time is a action, family, science
fiction film directed by Alex Winter.
Ben, Gwen, and Max must stop an extraterrestrial who plans to
open a gateway that leads to an alien invasion.
Ben Tennyson, played by Graham Phillips.
Eon, played by Christien Anholt.
Gwen Tennyson, played by Haley Ramm.
Sandra Tennyson, played by Beth Littleford.
Carl Tennyson, played by Don McManus.
Old Man, played by Sab Shimono.
Ben 10: Race Against Time (also known as Ben 10: The Movie) is a 2007 American superhero
film based on the animated television series Ben 10, created by Man of Action.
The working title was Ben 10 in the Hands of Armageddon.
Directed by Alex Winter, it premiered on November 21, 2007, in the
United States as a Cartoon Network original film.
The film explores themes of extraterrestrial technology,
superhero, transformation, alien, based on cartoon.
The tone is thought_provoking.